This is a woman's pants.
First, open a female model.
Double click on the screen window, click on the .
Find FemaleVR, then double click on the .
I drag her into the 3D window.
Open the .
Find B, BASIC, find D, PANTS, in the file PANTS, FEMALES, go to the camera, I will drag it to the 3D window, click on the dialogue box, click OK.
In the 2D window, use the adjustment panel tool to frame all the panels, place the panel to the 2D window, model shadow around, only half the panel.
Use the adjustment panel tool to frame the back panel in the 2D window.
On the panel, right-click on the panel, select the column link panel, align the panel, the panel, and the frame line, press SHIFT, set the level to the other side.
In the 3D tool bar, select all the positions to frame the 2D arrangement, pass the arrangement of the 2D window to the 3D window.
In the 3D vertical bar, select the display arrangement point, display the arrangement point, some arrangements are blocked.
In the 2D window, select all the panels, move the panels up and down in the 3D window, record the arrangements blocked.
The pocket and front panel exist separately.
In the 3D window, select the pocket panel.
Use the position tool to move the pocket panel to the back of the front panel.
In the 3D window, select the left front panel, use the position tool to move the left front panel to the top of the right front panel.
In the 2D tools, use the adjustment panel tool to move the left front panel.
In the 2D tool, use the adjustment panel tool, and press Shift to select the front pocket and pocket panels.
Left-click to select the Carolina panel in the menu, the symmetrical panel, the panel and the line, and copy the other half of the pants panel and the pocket.
Press Shift to place it horizontally to the other side.
In the 2D window, use the edit panel tool, press Shift to select the front pocket and pocket.
In the 3D window, press the left button on the model's arrangement point, and place the panel on the arrangement point.
You can adjust the position of the panel in the purple column arranged by the mouse.
In the 2D window, press Shift to select the left waist and right waist at the same time.
Move the mouse to the 3D window, click on the arrangement point of the forefoot, and place the panel.
Press the shortcut 8 to rotate the view to the rear view.
In the 2D window, select the front pocket panel panel and the jade panel panel.
In the 3D window, click on the arrangement point.
Wrap the panel around the virtual model.
Adjust the position of the panel in the attribute editor.
In the 2D window, select the back waist panel and press the button on the arrangement point of the 3D window.
Place the panel.
Rotate the view to the front view.
Switch the mouse to the 4th of the 3D vertical tool bar to display the arrangement point.
Hide the arrangement point.
Use the free-default tool.
Combine the pocket and jade panel to the pants panel.
In the part where the pocket panel and the pants panel merge, create a sewing line.
Change the sewing line type to Turned in the application editor.
After activating the simulation, the pocket will be more flat.
Use the sewing tool to mix the front and side parts of the pants.
Press the free-default tool on the long-press window.
Select mbm free sewing.
Combine the side parts according to the needs.
Press the return key to complete the sewing
Use the sewing tool to sew the back of the waist and the back of the waist
Use the sewing tool to sew the waist to the pocket and the pants
Use the sewing tool to sew the waist to the pocket
Choose the stitch in the 3D window
On the 2D panel, click on the button on the left to add a stitch
The stitch line will appear on the 2D pattern
And the emerged pattern will appear in the 3D window
In the 3D window, choose the stitch
Click on the button on the 2D panel marked as the stitch
The stitch line will appear on the 2D panel
The pattern marked as the stitch will appear in the 3D window
Use the move tool to choose the stitch
Adjust the angle of the stitch into the flipped Cultural Ruler
In the 3D tool bar, select the button button tool, in the 2D window, click on the button button first, then click on the button to close the eye, and then click on the button to close the eye.
In the 2D window, select the adjustment panel tool, and select the belt panel at the same time.
In the
view menu, scroll to the sticky stick option, click on the arrow to choose the sticky box next to it, and then click on the fire to make the panel naturally hanging on the virtual model.
After the simulation is complete, turn off the simulation.
Enter the canvas window, double click on the AVAILABLE file, enter the FemaleValue file, double-click to open the POS file, and then click on the AVAILABLE button.
Now, you can see the POS file in AVAILABLE.
In the POS file, you can see the POS file in the POS file, and you can see POS file in the POS file.
Double-click on FV203 or drag it into the 3D window.
Click on the menu to confirm.
Change the model's posture to a vertical one.
Enter the drawing window and double-click on the Fabric file.
Double-click on the Carton Coupling file and drag it to the Fabric E window.
The 7-way simulation will be used on 3D clothing.
In the 3D window, select the tool to improve the quality of the clothing.
Click on the dialogue box to confirm.
The simulation will be used on 3D clothing.
In the 3D